The fact that the brilliant Brianna Joy Gray and I had a two hour conversation, and this is what this person gleaned to highlight, tells you everything you need to know about their role in divide and conquer COINTELPRO practices.
Because y'all know I do not even address that woman by name.
She exists to me as just another part of the fascist milieu.
Did I call Angela Ryan Tiffany Cross Mean Girls?
Yeah, because I consider them to be mean girls.
I'm not saying that from a lack of experience.
That is how I feel about them.
I will gladly expound upon why, but y'all never asked for why.
Y'all just jumped to Amanda must be making it up, which I literally don't do.
And haven't yet.
I'm on Brianna Joy's podcast, but this person says Amanda has a lot of nerve and no mirrors.
Am I being compared to a member of the fascist milieu?
You can blame it on my tone, but the truth is folks are just really unsettled by my exposing their false idols.
They see this as a betrayal.
When what it really is, is an awakening.
And it's not just me doing it.
And I want to shout out all the other black folks who have woken up and woke me up in the process.
Y'all telling yourselves every time, the necessity to single me out, even when I'm not even the one saying the thing that was said, really just reveals your obsession.
And you would be so better served with channeling that obsession into support and into listening.
And I will tell you this, whatever you're projecting onto me is a reflection of that, which you have not addressed in yourself.
And I welcome you to do that in this season.
Because this season right here is going to be exponentially explosive.
And not only are you going to want to have the right people around you, not only are you going to want to have community and sisterhood, you're going to need to have clarity.
And that black skin, that's not going to be enough for you.
Not this time, baby.
Not all this black people need to stick together.
It's not real.
And I will not have identity politics continue to be weaponized against me while the actions themselves are not inclusive of me.
Shout out to all the people who watch Breonna Joy's podcast and left lovely comments about our conversation, about how it enlightened them, and about how it enriched them.
We truly appreciate you.